Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his trials, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The Royal Knights seemed to be maintaining the upper hand while attacking the Eye of the Midnight Sun's hideout.
But Justice Meraleona was about to defeat Raya for good.
We're the same, aren't we? So we should be able to talk things over.
Both sides are mad because we lost someone we loved.
I just want a kingdom where all of us get along and laugh together.
And when I'm the Wizard King, we'll have one. You'll see.
You imbecile, proudly proclaiming something so outrageous.
I think he's actually serious.
In fact, it reminds me of what someone else said once before.
If only the rest of the human race thought about it the way these guys do.
Then maybe...
No.
It's too late to stop now.
At the same time, the true intentions of Lykt, or rather Patry, were finally beginning to come to the surface.
Patry had once been betrayed by humans, forced to witness the violent mass murder of his fellow elves.
And so, since assuming the identity of Lykt, he had been working to resurrect his fallen companions.
For going back on their word, for killing the people I loved, they must pay.
I swear they will all be annihilated.
Indeed, the great rebirth will start with the humans.
What?
It can't be.
Yeah!
obeysolation
Wooow
何年先だって語って信じたいから今笑って
I want I want I
確かな約束が欲しくて
楽しくなりそうな方へ
一緒に走っていこうね
いつの間にか
君の背中
遠く感じてる
青い空にシャツが揺れる
未来向かい and blue
傾きに cry and pie
だから待って待って待って待って
置いてかないでいてよ
今すぐfly away
戦うtry again
だから待って待って待って
同じ場所にいたいよ
霞が痛い胸の痛みが
君に話したい僕の気持ちが
本当のことね
バリユパルダイ
就 perhaps
いやhed僕の全く動物は
仕組みに寂しい
不正解
そうですね
分かるいので
分かりない
は?
何じゃ無い一生じゃんよ
ここだよね
英 bullet kun
進umuzで
今も你是大学 stateの
sel気があるんだけど
Well, you see, uh...
Hurry up, spit it out.
I'm just itching to create another masterpiece.
Master Licht should be...
I don't understand.
What's going on here?
I didn't even do anything yet, I swear!
Whoa, this is crazy!
What kind of spell is that?
Ooh, this looks interesting!
Whoa, and finally,
We're goin' on right there!
Let's go.
Whoa.
Go, hey!
Whoa!
A shark,れe-beer.
Look there at the demon skull.
Oh, don't be afraid. It's all right.
There's nothing for us to be concerned about.
After all, we've got the magic knights.
We'll protect the Clover Kingdom from whoever dares to threaten it.
Asta, you know.
It looks like the sun's rising even though it's the middle of the night.
And those swords that appeared in the sky.
What's happening to this place?
What is that? So bright.
First the whole sky was covered with big shiny swords and now this too? I'm confused.
It's so bright.
I don't want the friendship, sure.
But I guess I should bring that up right now.
It might be another attack from the eye of the midnight sun.
It went out. But still, our friendship sparkles.
Hey, look at Ghosh. That's weird.
What's weird?
Your body is...
Yeah? What's the matter with it?
It's all glow-y.
What is that, Brie?
That just never ends, does it?
What the hell?
Oh, wow. Where'd this come from?
Not luck too.
This is so weird.
What is it?
I'm skating.
Man, it's one thing after another.
Come on. What's with the lights show?
You owe us an explanation before this is over. Do you understand?
Hey, answer me!
Too bad.
What is?
Your worthless human race is finished.
Oh, no. I have a bad feeling.
No. My friends.
What's happening?
Why do you look?
Klaus taps at me.
Don't use such a familiar tone with us.
You should know.
We are teammates or friends.
Be gone.
This key... is it?
Where did that light come from?
You alright? What happened?
I'll call the nearest Magic Knight Squad.
What do you think you're doing?
So, you finally made it here. Once you do, you've got the nerve to attack our guys. I'm gonna need an explanation for that.
It should be obvious that we're not the ones who once inhabited these forms.
No, we are the elves. A race that lived in this world long ago before we were slaughtered by you humans.
Is that right?
Precisely. Except this time it is humanity that will be eliminated. With no survivors. The same as before.
This thing is really shaping up to be an inconvenience for me. They did say something about being reborn into their true forms and gaining a whole bunch of magic power.
But I thought they meant those Eye of the Midnight Sun jerks would be the ones coming back.
It may be inconvenient, yes. But I promise you it won't take long at all.
If he's able to hit me with that spell, my most recent memories will be wiped away.
And looks like he's boosted his range and speed by a pretty big margin too.
Had enough.
Owen's recovery spell is different too. Way stronger and twisted somehow. Like he wants to break your body instead of healing it.
Get it together, Yami. Just grab them both and end this.
I don't recognize that corpse there. Is it someone who is important to you?
Not that it matters. He was a human so he was a repulsive sinner who deserved to die anyway.
Take that back.
If he's so precious to you, feel free to pay your respects while I obliterate his remains piece by piece.
You're not Marx and Owen. And I'm not gonna let you spew that garbage out of their mouths.
Go on. Charge right in. That's even easier. Memory magic. Form is cancel or attack.
Dark magic. Black hole. Dark magic. Dark closed. Lightless blade storm.
What?
Now why don't you stay put? I have to protect this country. A promise I made to a man both of you respected.
Man, what a mess. Those two aren't even combat mages. How did things get this out of hand?
What? Red roses?
My comrades.
Letting down your guard as soon as you awakened. It'll serve our mission better if you sleep within my spell. At least for now.
Hey, prickly princess. Long time no see, huh? I've never known you to cut people slack.
I don't know you at all. You seem capable for a human.
What's that? Powerful spells everywhere. The kingdom's being attacked again already?
Get the hell out of here. Now! If you don't escape, I'll waste you myself!
Let the buildings crumble all over town. As long as if the people live, a nation never dies.
But with so many of these jokers running around, the people might not hold out either.
The smell of these roses is covering up her magic power. This really isn't like her.
You know what? I always was good at hide-and-seek. Dark clothes! Light the flash!
Your intuition is sharp.
That's not it. It's cause of your key. It came through loud and clear.
My key?
No!
Gotta love key!
She's got Charlotte's key in all her moves, but the fighting style's different.
Her signature mid-range attacks are there, but now she's got a slew of close-range spells.
And that smell of scrambling her magic power. Not to mention her air-tight defense.
With that working against me, it won't be easy to knock her out.
Her roses. I heard they turned blue when she was cursed as a little girl.
What the hell?!
It's the curse on House Roselaine!
No!
Dammit!
You really made a mess of things, huh?
Made me spill the pasta I was eating all over the place.
I'm not a fan of chicks who prance into battle acting all smug when they have no reason to be.
I prefer women who are strong.
But you can lean on someone else every once in a while.
You know how you can find lots of other strong people to lean on?
By joining the Magic Knights.
I'm a bit fuzzy on the details, but I think the curse got lifted back then, too.
If that's the case, then you'd think the roses would have changed color.
Well, she is an elf inside.
Maybe the mark of the curse went away now that she's not human anymore.
This must be Charlotte Roselaine's original briar magic.
The Charlotte I used to know was a determined woman who used her curse to her advantage and made herself stronger.
And now you'd let someone take over your body and magic for their own purposes?
I'm disappointed in you!
Char, no!
This chick?
What's with you?
You...
Attacked us.
I don't understand.
How could you?
Tell me.
You didn't mean to hurt us.
Right, Char?
What's wrong?
Impudent, sniveling human.
Don't address me like a friend.
You mean nothing to me.
But Char...
Listen, she's being controlled by some kind of magic.
It's not her.
So what are we supposed to do now?
You could just leave your boss lady to me.
What?
You showed up at a good time, though.
Huh? What is that?
I want you to take this orb and go somewhere safe, alright?
Hey! I refuse to take orders from men, forget it!
Is this really the time to be worried about that kind of crap?
I said no!
There's a hero inside there.
Show some respect for...
What are you doing?
I won't let Char be rescued by a man, either!
Hang on, you can't just barrel in there!
Yeah, well, it's either that or abandon her!
Trust me, I can snap her out of it!
Now, Earth magic!
Malti!
Char's hyper-concentrated magic field is keeping me from casting my spells properly.
That's a tough fight, even for a captain.
Does this mean I'll be totally helpless to stop her?
No, not after all she's done for me.
Char was the person who saved my life!
I'll make her wake up!
Even if I get killed in the process!
Forget that!
We're under orders to protect the people and stay alive, which means that's what we're gonna do!
It's not that I don't understand where you're coming from!
Then let go!
Not until I'm finished!
You have to survive Dum-Dum, not just for her's sake, but for his too!
No!
Mock my words!
Nobody gets near Char on my watch, especially not some low-life man!
Please save Char!
The Blue Rose Knights be there, Captain!
I'm counting on you!
And stand down!
I got this!
You missed your chance to run away!
I'm not planning to!
Dark magic!
Black hole!
Your subordinates crying!
You're just gonna let them do what they want?
That's what a weakling would do, and you're not weak!
I know you're not!
You're quite strong!
I respect you!
This magic power is unbelievable!
Black hole won't nearly be enough to absorb it all!
One good blast from that, and half the town will be blown to smithereens,
taking countless lives with it!
Ha! You have my respect!
You've had it all along!
That's why!
Whatever it takes, I'll save you!
Dark magic!
Crimson Vines!
Dark blow!
Dimension Splash!
You guys, what's wrong?
It's just so... beautiful!
It's just like with Beto and the others. It feels so... evil!
Why's that kind of magic power coming from you?
What's that kind of magic power coming from you?
It's just so... beautiful!
It's just like with Beto and the others. It feels so evil!
Why's that kind of magic power coming from you?
What's that kind of magic power coming from you?
It's just like with Beto and the others. It feels so evil. Why is that kind of magic power coming from you?
I don't need no money I don't need no魔力はいらない自力で挑んでミラクル起きること願い
微力ながら1mmずっとビリビリ切り込んでく世界を巻き込んでく My disability is my ability逆にそれが俺のエネルギー
どうしても自らを見失って嫌いになって負けそうになったら Just cry out loud
傷つく音に 傷つく音に 立ち向かう勇気へと導いてく Our treasure
裏切らないのは 最高に There is love
かざした誓い光が握る Treasure
Clover clips
Radiant Royal Noel and the letter N
Numb
This is weird. I can't feel my feet
Nutrition
I'm boiling alive but at least I'm part of a healthy diet
Needle work
Look at that. My tapestry's almost finished
Not bad
Nails
My hands are still pretty sore from all that needle work though
Noelle
They love me
Well I am royalty
Whoa! All of a sudden those midnight sun jerks started shining really bright and now they're crazy powerful! Wait, real? What are you attacking us for?
Black Clover page 97 overwhelming disadvantage
I hope the captain knows what to do